https://www.savox.com/privacy-policy

Log In
Menu
Products
.
Audio
Video
Data
Systems
.
Concepts
.
Customer solutions
Services
About Savox
.
Data
Search:
Search
Products
Products.
Audio.
Communication Controllers.
Push to Talk Units.
Savox C-C440
Savox BT-Com
Savox Lite-COM
Remote Speaker Microphones.
Savox C-C550
Savox BTR-155
Savox RSM-30
Savox Mobile RSM
Communication Hubs.
Savox TRICS
Headsets.
Helmet-Com Headsets.
Savox HC-200
Behind the Neck Headsets.
Savox L-H
Hearing Protection Headsets.
Savox Noise-COM 200
Throat Mic Headsets.
Savox T-M, T-C
Confined Space Com Systems
Data.
Computers and routers
Life Detectors
Rescue Kits
Video.
Systems
.
Concepts
.
Customer solutions
Services
About Savox
.
Privacy policy of Savox Communications
WHAT INFORMATION DOES SAVOX COLLECT ABOUT ME?
Personal informationYou may choose to provide personal information to Savox, for example via our ‘Contact Us’ page, or other forms within our website and microsites. Personal information may typically comprise your name, email address, postal address, telephone or mobile number.
HOW WILL THE INFORMATION BE USED BY SAVOX?
Savox will only use your information to:
Provide you with the information you have requested and to follow up on your enquiry once it has been fulfilled.For administration purposes (for example if you apply for a job with us).Send you information about ourselves and our products and services, but only where you have given us permission to do so.
WHEN WILL SAVOX CONTACT ME?
We will contact you:
In response to your request for information or your request to be contacted in relation to Savox services and marketing initiatives.To follow up business opportunities with you at a later date.For marketing purposes where you have specifically agreed to this.
HOW LONG WILL SAVOX KEEP MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We will keep your information only as long as is necessary to fulfill the request you make or administer any services you choose to receive. We may contact you periodically after this to keep in touch with you unless you tell us not to, you can opt-out at any time. No information will be kept for longer than is necessary.
WILL SAVOX SHARE MY INFORMATION WITH ANYONE ELSE?
We will keep your information confidential except where disclosure is required or permitted by law (for example to government bodies and law enforcement agencies).
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
This Privacy Policy applies solely to the personal data collected by Savox and does not apply to third party websites. Savox is not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
From time to time we may update this policy so you may wish to check again in the future by visiting our website.
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact:
Savox CommunicationsKeilaranta 15 B02150 Espoo, Finland
Email: savox@savox.com
Savox has a global presence.
Contact the closest Savox partner near you for more information.
